《打工姐妹花》前情提要
Previously on 2 Broke Girls.
是邀请参加大都会博物馆的年度晚会
No, this is invitation to Metropolitan Museum annual gala.
你看邀请名单上的名流
I mean, look at all the celebrities that are on the list
玛莎·斯图尔特
Martha Stewart,
栗宝 栗宝 宝贝你来啦
Chestnut! Chestnut, hi, baby, hi.
没错 我现在当司机还有新标语
Yes, I have a new car service and slogan:
"放松坐好 你不喊停 我绝不停下"
"lie back and I will ride you till you tell me to stop."
不会吧 这是强尼画的
I think this is Johnny's art. No way.
当然不会 强尼只是小角色
"No way" is right. Johnny's a nobody.
这画谁画的啊
Yo, what's the deal with this art?
一个街头艺术家
It's a street artist.
最近还挺火热的
Everyone's getting really into him now.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
几个月前他也想跟我"搞"得火热呢
He was trying to get into me a few months ago.
画下句点 和你道别 我很快就要...
and I came to say good-bye because I'm...
结婚了
Getting married.
起码你跟你那女朋友修成正果了
Well, at least you and your girlfriend worked it out.
其实我们分手了
Actually, we broke up.
我是要跟几个月前认识的另一个女人结婚
This is someone I met a couple months ago.
我们从没一帆风顺过
Nothing ever does work out for us.
然后听到自己瞎扯的那些
And then I hear myself saying all that ridiculous stuff
跟家政女皇合作的事情
about us talking to Martha Stewart at the gala.
那简直就是痴人说梦嘛
I mean, what was that? It's insane.
是吗
Is it?
没错 就是要我们去跟踪玛莎·斯图尔特
I am talking about us stalking Martha Stewart!
那我们该穿什么去舞会呢 灰姑娘
What else are we gonna wear to the ball, Cinderella?
难道防火巷里的老鼠会帮我们织礼服吗
Are the rats in the alley gonna whip us up some ball gowns?
我们又没有个神仙教母
I mean, it's not exactly like we have a fairy godmother.
姑娘们
Hey, look, girls!
我在我最爱的店里买了皇冠跟魔棒呢
I got myself a crown and a wand at Rhinestoned.
苏菲 感谢你慷慨解囊
Sophie, this is so generous of you
愿意帮我们买晚宴穿的裙子
to offer to buy us dresses for the gala,
不过尽管我的鞋子很开心能
but as much as my shoes love being back
回到"出生地"
in their place of birth...
哇 你的鞋子是在这"出生"的呀
Oh, your shoes were born here?
我的鞋在中国出生
Mine were born in China,
然后被我从网上鞋店"领养"回家
but I adopted them at Payless.
或许我们应该去寄卖店
Maybe we should find something cheaper,
淘两件便宜货
at one of those consignment stores.
"寄卖店"
"Consignment stores"?
拜托 你当我们是游牧民族啊
Come on, what are we, gypsies?
要去华丽的盛会 就得盛装打扮啊
This is big fancy ball. We need ball gowns.
我从来不喜欢参加舞会[蛋蛋]
Never really been a fan of balls.
老实说 我总觉得它们挺碍事
In fact, always thought they got in the way,
可我们始终是来了
but here we are.
如果我们要带着小蛋糕
Well, we do have to look amazing
接近玛莎·斯图尔特 就必须得打扮得美美的
if we're approaching Martha Stewart with a cupcake,
钱我们会想办法还你的
so we'll find a way to pay you back
不然先从免费帮你打扫房子开始好了
and start by doing some cleaning jobs for you for free.
不用
No!
我每年都捐钱给慈善机构
Every year I give money to charity,
而且相比那些孩子阴暗的假笑
and I like you two girls way more than the babies
我更喜欢你们俩姑娘
with the broken smiles.
所以别担心 姐可是带足了钱
So don't worry. I got plenty of cash.
哇 一捆百元大钞
Aww, a roll of hundreds.
我以前圣诞袜也用这个填充
Reminds me of my Christmas stocking stuffers.
今天真好玩
Yeah, this is fun day.
我就像理查·基尔 而你们俩是我的风月佳人
I'm like Richard Gere and you're my two hookers.
听你这么一说
Well, when you put it like that,
我心里舒服多了
I'm a little more comfortable.
下午好 有什么需要帮忙的吗
Good afternoon. How can I help you?
你好 我们赶时间
Hi, how are you? We don't have a lot of time.
下午6点就得上班
We have to be at work by 6:00.
麻烦把店里最好的春款晚礼服拿出来
Can you show us your best formal spring couture?
或许你们去普通成衣店
Perhaps you ladies might be more comfortable
比较合适吧
down in ready-to-wear.
都说了我们赶时间
As I said, we're in a bit of a rush.
如果你能摆低姿态 快点把衣服拿出来
We might move a little quicker if you dropped the attitude
我们就能快点甩钱走人
and picked up some dresses.
把你那捆大钞露出来
Show her your wad.
很高兴为你们服务
Let's look at some dresses.
对了 要像电影那样
Yeah, and get us some champagne,
给我们上点香槟哦
like in the movies.
Nicki Minaj - Starship
一 二
One, two...
阿憨 你踮脚是为了显得个子高点吗
Han, did you just go up on your tiptoes like a big boy?
我不知道今天会需要拍照
Well, I wasn't expecting a photo opportunity.
所以我没穿汤姆·克鲁斯也爱穿的增高鞋来
And I left my Tom Cruise man-heels at home.
麦克斯 别说他了
Max, give him a break.
这男人矮的都当不上马师
This is a man who was too short to be a jockey.
奥列格 给我相机
Oleg, give me your camera.
我得审核照片
I must approve picture.
我们都拍了三次了
We've taken it three times already.
阿憨 如果你想要奶子走光照 就直说
Han, if you want a nip slip, just ask.
我的衣服这么漂亮 不适合参与这种话题
My dress is too pretty for this conversation,
所以我还是去冰箱把蛋糕拿出来吧
so I'm gonna go get the cupcake from the refrigerator.
那我先为姑娘们热一下我的加长新轿车
And I'm going to warm up my new town car for the ladies.
新车
New?
如果现在是2002年 那就是新车
What is this, 2002?
我倒希望
I hope so,
这样我就有机会重新与你相遇
then I will have chance to meet you for first time all over again.
这可不是专职司机该讲的话
Now this is not professional driver talk.
舞会仙女婆婆 你这是闹哪样
Hey, fancy ball Buster, what's your deal?
是你告诉他要有梦想与冲劲
You told him to get a dream and a drive,
现在他做到了
and he did.
麦克斯 我有两个痛处
Max, I have two sore spots.
一个是相信男人
Trusting men and...
另一个是这里 那个牙买加疯子
And here, where that crazy Jamaican
把我的头发接得太紧了
wove my extensions too tight.
我在想等下车之后
I'm thinking I should wait to put the cupcake
我再把小蛋糕放进小蛋糕包里
in the cupcake purse till we get out of the car.
我要用混酒面粉加枫蜜培根小蛋糕
We want our beer batter maple bacon cupcake
作为我们小蛋糕业务的招牌
to represent our cupcake business.
她又刷新记录了
We have a new record.
一口气居然说了四次小蛋糕
She cupcake four times in one speech.
我们该走了
We should go.
这个点从布鲁克林去上东区该堵死了
Upper East Side from Brooklyn at this time of day is crazy.
可我们来这是为了让厄尔看看
But we came in here to show Earl.
可能厄尔觉得今晚休息
Maybe Earl decided not to come
就不过来了吧
since he had the night off.
麦克斯 我们必须在一开始就到场
Max, we really should be there at the start.
那是偷偷接近玛莎·斯图尔特的最佳时机
That's prime Martha Stewart stalking time.
你说得对 玛莎"很可能"
You're right. And Martha will probably
会需要提早离场 回家干活
have to leave early to get up to bake;
这方面我也经验丰富
a little something I knows about.
我和玛莎唯一的区别是
The only difference between Martha and I
她无需担心会吵醒
is she probably doesn't have to worry about
睡在烤箱四英尺之外的室友
waking up her roommate who lives four feet from the oven.
除此之外 毫无差别啊
But otherwise, twinsies!
等等 等等
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
厄尔 慢点 你有心脏病
Earl, slow down, your heart.
抱歉来晚了 女士们
Sorry I'm late, ladies.
我再跑快一点 警察会以为我是在逃嫌犯呢
But if I run any faster, the cops tend to pull guns on me.
在花店耽搁了一会儿
Got held up at the florist shop,
还好及时赶到 给 女士们
but I made it. Here you go, ladies.
厄尔 你还专门给我们买花啊
Aww, Earl, you got us flowers?
腕花
Wrist corsages.
希望现在还流行这个
I hope they're still in style.
经典永垂不朽 厄尔
They're a classic, Earl.
跟你一样
Like you.
这趟跑得真值
Mmm, that was worth the run.
走吧 女士们
Let's go, ladies.
奥列格等着载你们驶向目的地
Oleg is waiting to drive you.
而你 载我驶向墓地
And you drive me crazy.
是呀是呀 这话跟海军陆战队说去
Yeah, yeah. Tell it to the marines.
给 厄尔 帮我拿着手机
Here, Earl, take my phone.
装了蛋糕 我的手包就装不下手机了
I can't fit it in the purse with my cupcake.
祝你玩得愉快
Have the best time in the world.
代我向"巨根"杰克曼问好
And say hello to "Huge" Jackman for me.
这可不是好兆头
That is not a good sign.
这车喷出来的烟比
That car is smoking harder than
鲍勃·马利在斯塔法教日喷得还狠
Bob Marley on a rasta holiday.
苏菲 如果我的表弟有利说
Sophie, if my cousin Yuri said he would be here
他会在半小时内带着工具来修车
in half hour with parts to fix,
他就一定会在半小时内到
he will be here in half hour.
话说这都过了40分钟了吧
Actually, it's been 40 minutes.
你的表弟就跟你一样
Your cousin is like you.
死活不来[射]
He takes too long to come.
真新鲜
Oh, this is news.
女人突然开始喜欢男人早早完事了
Suddenly a woman wants a man to finish fast.
拜托
Oh, please.
做爱又不是邮轮可以慢慢开
Sex is not a carnival cruise.
我很忙的
I'm a busy woman.
前脚上船 后脚下船
You get on, you get off.
我能来一口吗
Can I get a hit off that?
我猜就只能干等了
We'll just have to wait, I guess.
如果我还住在曼哈顿 我可以打个车
I mean, if I still lived in Manhattan, I'd hail a cab.
但我们是在荒郊野岭 所以求助无门
But that's not gonna happen out here in the boondocks!
再说了 即使打得起车
Plus, even if we could afford a cab,
我们也会被困在高峰时期无尽的堵车中
we'd be stuck forever in rush hour gridlock.
你能小点声吗
Could you take it down a notch?
嬉皮士们都看过来了
Hipsters are starting to look at us
好像我们入戏太深似的
like we're trying too hard.
阿憨去哪里了
Where did Han go?
他说他可能有办法
He said he might have a plan.
万能的主呀
Oh, my lord and Taylor!
那小玩意儿居然会骑
That little mother can ride.
你们俩就像童话里的两位公主
You two look like two princesses in a fairy tale.
你怕不怕
Are you feeling safe?
如果我们骑的是
I couldn't feel any safer
塑胶小马 我就不怕
if we were riding a rubber into town.
那我们走啦 再见 各位
Here we go. Bye, guys.
-再见 -走吧 栗宝
- Bye. - Go, Chestnut!
快看 你也看见了吧
Oh, check it out. You see what I see?
你好 警官大人
Hello, officers.
我们在去舞会的路上
We're on way to the ball down the street,
我们想问能不能请你们
and we were wondering if we could please leave
帮我看一下马
our horse with your horses?
你们也不必浪费时间
And I can save you the time
做酒精浓度测试
on the breathalyzer test;
我们没喝醉
No, we are not drunk
也没在玩未婚女子派对的寻宝游戏
or on some bachelorette party scavenger hunt.
我们的车在布鲁克林坏了
Our car broke down in Brooklyn,
我们是从布鲁克林大桥骑过来的
so we rode over the Brooklyn bridge and up.
你骑着马在布鲁克林大桥上跑啊
You rode a horse across the Brooklyn bridge?
真是酷毙了
That's badass.
没错 同时也违法了
Yes... And illegal.
其实我们走的是隧道
In that case, we took the tunnel.
没问题 我们可以帮忙
Well, I think we can help you two ladies.
不可能 戴夫 我们在值班呢
Not gonna happen, Dave. We're on duty.
警官大人 我们已经迟到了
Officers, we're already a little late.
恕我直言 我们真没时间
And with all due respect, we don't have time
玩好警察坏警察的游戏
to play good cop, bad cop.
不过你们俩是 帅警察超帅警察
Or in your cases, hot cop, hot cop.
没问题 我们可以帮忙
Well, I think we can help you ladies.
先扶你们俩下来吧
Let's get you down off of there.
裙子低胸那个我来扶
I got the one in the low-cut.
谢谢帅警官和超帅警官
Thanks officer hot and officer hotter.
麦克斯 你穿着长裙
Max, I'm really impressed with how well
还能活动自如 真让我意外
you're maneuvering around in that long skirt.
我在中世纪餐馆工作时穿过女仆装
Yeah, I was a serving wench at a medieval times restaurant.
不用端着装满
It's a breeze when I'm not carrying
火鸡腿和啤酒的盘子 更让我身轻如燕
a tray loaded with Turkey legs and ale.
预定零售台在那里
There's the "will call" Table.
你走前面 我躲在你后面
Walk in front and I'll hide behind you,
因为我是全纽约最遭人恨的女人
as I'm the most hated woman in New York.
所以我是来当人肉盾牌的吗
So basically, I'm a human shield?
你上面比较"有料" 能抵挡一切
Well, you have more up here to stop anything.
-麦克斯 -怎么了
- Max! - What?
有人掏枪吗
Did someone pull a gun?
我就知道会有状况发生
I knew that was gonna happen.
不是 我尖叫是因为我看见
No, I screamed because I saw the couple
那对让我爸锒铛入狱的夫妇
whose sworn statement put my father in prison.
麦克斯
Max!
有人用硫酸泼你的小脸吗
Acid in your pretty face?
抱歉 我熬夜翻你的仇恨信
Sorry, I stayed up all night reading
看看人们想怎么把你千刀万剐
what people want to do to you in your hate mail.
又怎么了
What was it?
我蹲下太快 可能弄脏了我的小蛋糕
I went down so fast, I may have smeared my cupcake.
这是我听过最黄最"纯洁"的事了
That's the filthiest sounding clean thing I ever heard.
还好没事
It's fine. Good.
现在去拿两个会破坏我们华服整体美感的
Now let's go get those cheap plastic security bracelets
廉价塑料安检手环
that ruin our expensive gowns.
-能告诉我你的名字吗 -卡洛琳
- Can I get your name? - Caroline...
钱宁
Channing.
抱歉 没听见
I'm sorry, what?
卡洛琳
Caroline...
钱宁
Channing.
你搞什么 快说名字
What's with you? Just say your name.
钱宁
Channing.
你刚是说钱宁吗 卡洛琳·钱宁
Did you say channing? Caroline channing?
慢着 你是那个卡洛琳·钱宁吗
Wait, are you that Caroline channing?
对 我亲自打过电话问过主办方
Shh, yes, and I personally called the R.S.V.P. Number.
肯定有我的名字
It has to be there.
钱宁 钱宁 钱宁
Channing, channing, channing...
没 我没看见有"卡洛琳·钱宁"
No, I don't see "Caroline channing."
或许在我的名字下
Maybe it's under my name.
麦克斯·布莱克 我们是一起的
Max black. I'm with her.
布莱克 没没没 我没看见任何叫布莱克[黑人]的
Black... no, no, no, I don't see any blacks here.
你是说除了在场的黑人保安吗
You mean besides the ones working security?
我问下派对策划人保罗·普拉特吧
Let me check with Paul Platt, the party planner.
他的助手正在跟他通电话呢
He's on the phone with him right now.
-布洛迪 -不是吧
- Hey, Brody. - Oh, no.
名单有点问题
There's a problem with the list.
她不在名单上 就是她
She's not on it. Her.
卡洛琳·钱宁
Caroline channing.
保罗 卡洛琳·钱宁来了
Paul, I've got Caroline channing,
可她不在名单上
and she's not on the list.
后面派对的各位麻烦等等
If everybody in this line could just wait until
我们要处理下卡洛琳·钱宁突发状况
we get the Caroline channing situation under control...
如果你敢在大声喊一次"卡洛琳·钱宁"
If you say "Channing" One more time,
老娘就把你的喉头给扯出来
I'm going to actually pull your voice box out.
做起来比听起来要暴力一百倍哦
And its s so much more violent than it sounds.
好的 保罗 我会转告他们
Yes, Paul, I'll tell them.
出现了点小状况
There's been a little mix-up.
五分钟后就放你们进去
Five more minutes will get you right in.
你们进不去
You're not getting in.
就这样吧 至少我们试了
Well, that's it. We tried.
-我们尽力了 -不要
- We gave it our best shot. - Oh, no.
这是我这辈子
This is the closest I have ever gotten
最接近成功的一次
to anything in my life almost working out.
-我们不能放弃 -那我们怎么进去
- We are not giving up. - How are we getting in?
-这全是保安 -对 这里全是
- Security's everywhere. - Yeah, out here,
但服务员入口处没有
but not at the servers' entrance.
我去年不是来过吗
I catered this last year.
没错 我们要走后门啦
That's right, we're going backdoor.
那女的打了我一拳
That lady just punched me.
我就知道会有状况发生
I knew that was gonna happen!
你就这么大摇大摆地走进来啊
So you can just walk in here?
这里谁都可以随便进的吗
Anyone can just walk right in?
去年我是靠跟里克
Well, it helps that last year
那个帐篷保安亲热 才进来的
I made out with the tent flap guard, Rico,
但基本上谁都能进
but basically, yeah, anyone.
当我回想起过去
When I think of all the times
我把钱包仍在桌子上跑掉时
I left my purse on a table here unattended,
我的心在颤抖啊 颤抖
I shudder... Shudder.
好啦 我们不装成服务员
Okay, so we can't get in the actual building
进不去主楼
without being caterers,
所以我们得换上制服
so we have to change into those uniforms.
慢着
Wait.
你刚可没有跟我说
You never mentioned anything about
需要把礼服换掉哦
a rent-a-clothes situation.
想进去总得付出点代价嘛
Small price to pay for us making it.
是吗 这真的是小小的代价吗
Is it? Is it a small price to pay?
快点 我们得跟踪大明星呢
Hurry, we have a superstar to stalk!
我原以为我会很抗拒 但我现在蛮喜欢的
I thought I would hate it, but I'm kind of into it.
我超像加奈儿·梦奈的
I'm very Janelle Monae.
不 你是加奈儿·恶梦吧
No, you're Janelle I-have-no-Monae.
那我们的礼服怎么办
What are we going to do with our dresses?
不能把它们留在这里 我进里面还要穿呢
We can't leave them out here. I need them inside.
我必须美美的见玛莎·斯图尔特
I have to look amazing when I meet Martha Stewart.
我们穿什么去见她很重要吗
What does it matter what we're wearing?
反正我们是两个拿着小蛋糕
We're still going to be the two crazy girls
四处找她的疯婆子
chasing her down with a cupcake.
所以衣着就更重要啦
That's why it matters.
我知道了 这里
I know. Here.
帮我把架子拿出来
Help me get the shelves out of this.
我们可以把礼服挂里面
We can hang our dresses in here
-然后把它们推进去 -真聪明
- and push them in. - Brilliant.
这柜子有点像我以前的LV旅行衣柜
Kind of like the Louis Vuitton travel wardrobe I used to have.
或者像我妈生我时的那个电梯
Or the service elevator I was born in.
借过 滚汤热菜
Coming through, hot food.
小心 热气腾腾 天啊 热死了
Look out, very hot! Man, it's hot.
你是个服务员 不是气象员
You're a waiter, not a weatherman.
美女
Hey, pretty girls,
我喜欢你鼓捣大铁箱的方式
I like the way you push around that big steel box
你何不过来 让我打一炮
why don't you come over here and I'll have sex with you?
这样赤裸裸的言语 真让人感激
A display like that really makes you appreciate
奥列格恰如其分的调戏
Oleg's nuanced wit.
好吧 我们直接去女厕所换衣服吧
Okay, let's go right to the ladies room so we can change.
是走这边 还是那边
Is it that way or that way?
怎么了
What?
强尼也在
Shh, Johnny!
怎么会邀请他
How'd he get invited?
这过去可是私人聚会
This used to be an exclusive event.
他现在是"成功人士"
He's "Made it,"
当然去"成功人士"该去的地方
he goes where "Made it" People go.
你干嘛躲着那个混蛋啊
Why are we hiding from that lowlife?
如果他看见我穿着另一身服务生制服
If he sees me in another waiter uniform,
我永远都是穿制服的可怜姑娘
I'm the sad girl always in the uniform.
如果他在舞会上看见我穿着礼服出现
If he sees me in that dress at the ball,
那他可以回家擦眼泪了
he can suck it.
女厕所 在那边
Ladies room, that way.
女厕所就在这里
The ladies room is right down here.
用力推
Push harder.
用力啊 你难道想穿成这样见玛莎吗
Harder! Do you want Martha to see you dressed like that?
-闪开 借过 -让一下
- Move! Coming through! - Excuse us.
食物紧急情况
Food emergency.
我的手指 手指 手指 手指
Fingers, fingers, fingers, fingers.
借过 借过
Coming through, coming through.
-让一下 -看着点 红姑娘
- Excuse us. - Look alive, red!
-我差点撞到你了 -等等
- I almost hit you. - Hold up.
你俩等等 这是怎么回事
Now just hold up. What is going on right now?
你不能带食物进这儿
You can't bring food in here.
这不是食物 谁会带食物进来呀
Oh, it's not food. That would be weird.
这是礼服 我们得换上它
It's dresses. We have to change into these,
因为她要让一个男人刮目相看
'cause she has this guy she wants to impress,
而我要换是因为
and I have to change into it
我在跟踪玛莎·斯图尔特
because I'm stalking Martha Stewart.
啊哦 我一定是个烂间谍
Ooh, I'd be a terrible spy.
通常在一晚结束后
Usually I don't get the long stories
才有人跟我讲故事
till the end of the night,
那时 姑娘们会哭着
and by then, the girls are crying
求我给她们长长脑子 缩缩奶子
and begging me for Wisdom and tic tacs.
我先去
I'll go first.
把这"胸器"塞进一条裙子 需要点时间
I have to get two of these in one dress.
女士 请问你有鞋拔子吗
Miss, do you have a shoehorn?
快出来 香奈儿的鞋
Come on, Chanel shoes!
快出来 山寨香奈儿
Come on, Chanel knockoffs.
你怎么还不换衣服
Why are you not dressed yet?
因为女人上厕所慢死了
'Cause ladies take forever.
都怪那些塑身裤
It's all the spanx.
去 用我那间 我要伸个头出去
Well, go, use my stall. I want to go stick my head out,
看看能不能发现强尼
and see if I can scope out Johnny.
不 女士 不 这不公平
No, ma'am, no! Not fair, ma'am.
试试残疾人厕所 这边
Try the handicapper. This side.
好主意
Good idea.
我今晚真是霉运不断
I cannot get a break tonight.
-麦克斯 -强尼
- Psst, yo, Max. - Johnny!
你在找谁
Who are you looking for?
达美乐披萨仔
The Dominos guy.
我躲在里面是因为再过五分钟
I was hiding in there, 'cause five more minutes,
披萨就能免费吃
the pizza's free.
我还期待能遇见你呢
I was hoping I'd run into you.
也没什么好见的
Eh, no big deal.
当然不是 你看起美呆了
Pretty big deal. You look amazing.
美得我蛋疼菊紧 虎躯一震
Amazing. I will go as far as amaze-balls.
多谢夸奖
Thanks.
你看起像广告里那种
You look like a guy in a commercial
藏着戒指和小狗的男人
who has a ring and puppy hidden somewhere.
你能相信吗
Can you believe it?
咱俩身穿锦衣华服
We're both at this shmancy thing.
我们变化真大呀
Look how far we've gotten.
其实当你静心一想
Actually, when you think about it,
你会发现我们都没变
we didn't get very far at all.
对 你说得对 的确没变
Nope, you're right. We didn't.
为什么
Yeah, why?
时机不对吧
Timing, I guess.
时机
Timing?
随你怎么说吧
Okay, whatever.
从现在开始 每当我想起你
You know, from now on, when I think of you,
我会想着你身穿礼服 而不是制服的样子
I'm gonna think of you in this and not the uniform.
从现在开始
You know, from now on,
或许你就不该再想我
maybe you shouldn't think of me at all.
走啦 曼哈顿先生
Gotta go, Mr. Manhattan.
太棒了 卡洛琳 你在哪里
That was awesome! Caroline, where are you?
我快穿好了
I'm almost dressed.
我刚跟强尼来了次完美的当面告别
I just had the perfect in-your-face good-bye with Johnny.
说到"当面"
And speaking of "in your face,"
他当着我的面 还直勾勾盯着我的胸
he couldn't take his eyes off my boobs...
谁让他要结婚
Boobs that he can never have,
这对美胸从此跟他告别了
now that he's getting married.
靠 妹子 你真美 你晚点有活动吗
Damn, girl, you look good. What you doing later?
能给我你的电话吗
Can I get your number?
天啊 小蛋糕在我的包包有点被砸碎了
Oh, no, the cupcake got a little smushed in my purse.
我们不能拿给玛莎·斯图尔特了
We can't show this to Martha Stewart now.
干嘛不可以
Sure, we can.
你觉得她没被人用蛋糕糊过脸吗
You think she never had a cupcake smush on her?
我觉得没有
I doubt that very much.
玛莎·斯图尔特是个完人
Martha Stewart is perfect.
超凡脱俗 脚不着地
Her feet don't even touch the ground.
可能连厕所都不需要上
The woman probably doesn't even go to the bathroom.
人无完人
Martha Stewart's hardly perfect.
今晚过得好吗
And how are you this evening?
你说得对 人无完人 她也不例外
No, you're right, Martha Stewart isn't perfect.
这话我可没说过
Oh, I never said that!
其实我听说她超爱虐男人的
In fact, I hear she's a real ballbuster.
你什么都没听见
You did not hear that.
真的 超爱虐男人 你知道吗
Yep, a real ballbuster, you know?
我什么都不知道
No, I do not know.
能递块毛巾给我吗
Would you mind handing me a towelette please?
一块就行 谢谢
Oh, one's fine. Thank you so much.
但就是因为玛莎·斯图尔特那么强悍
But the fact that Martha Stewart is so tough...
卡洛琳 你得马上出来
Caroline, you need to get out here right now.
那么爱虐男人
The fact that she is a real ballbuster...
神啊 救救我吧
Oh, dear God, help me.
所以我才那么喜欢她和敬重她
Is what I like and respect about her.
那个女人是个天才
I mean, the woman's a genius.
越来越有意思了
Now it's getting interesting.
而且 你不能听信传闻
And besides, you can't really believe gossip.
瞧瞧我收到的仇恨信
Look at all that hate mail I got
多少人骂我贱货啊
with people calling me a bitch,
可其实我不是
and I'm not a bitch.
这有待商议
Well, that's debatable.
-玛莎·斯图尔特 你好 -你好啊
- Martha Stewart, hi. - Hello.
我是卡洛琳 这是我的生意伙伴麦克斯
I'm Caroline, and this is my business partner, Max,
我们的小蛋糕生意刚起步
and we have a start-up cupcake business.
妹子 你不是吧 都这样了你还不放手啊
Dude, are you serious? You're still going for it.
我知道这非常不合时宜
I know this is highly inappropriate,
但我们今晚带了个小蛋糕过来
but we brought a cupcake here tonight
衷心希望你能尝一口
in hopes that you might taste it.
所以你要我在女厕所
So you want me to taste your cupcake
吃你的小蛋糕
in the ladies room.
还有比这更不合时宜的吗
What's inappropriate about that?
我们的生意刚起步 不抓住机会不行啊
We're a start-up business. We've got to take risks.
这位是麦克斯 她是烘培师
This is Max. She's the baker.
-你是烘培师啊 -我是烘培师
- You're the baker. - I'm the baker.
看起来蛮吸引人的
Hm, it looks quite appealing.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我知道这是社交场合
I know this is a social event,
很抱歉把它弄得那么商业化
so I'm so sorry for making it about business.
当你自己出来打拼事业时
When you're in business for yourself,
你必须得把每一个场合
you have to take every situation
都当作是商机
as a business opportunity.
瞧 我还随身带着五本书呢
Look, I have five of these in here.
我超爱看你的家政杂志
I love your magazine.
我阅读上面每一篇文章
I read every single issue
直到我被抓到不是看病 只是去偷看杂志
until they realized I didn't even go to that doctor.
我要说一句
Well, in spite of the fact
你至今还没有洗手
that you have not yet washed your hands...
我刚是在里面换衣服的
I was just changing my dress in there.
-我会尝一口 -真的吗
- I'll taste it. - You will?
我喜欢你的闯劲
I like your entrepreneurial drive.
而且我深深地觉得
And I have a feeling that it's actually
只有尝一口 才能活着离开这儿
the only way I'm gonna get out of here alive.
这是我们的酒混面粉加枫蜜培根的
That is our beer batter maple bacon
特制春假小蛋糕
spring break cupcake.
-名字不错 -谢谢
- Hm, clever name. - Thank you.
不过有点糊了 真可惜
It is a little smushed, though. That's unfortunate.
我都说了
I told you.
蛮好吃的
Mmm. Quiet tasty.
我喜欢
I like it.
你们有名片吗
Do you girls have a card?
拿出来 拿出来 快拿出来
Get it out, get it out, get it out.
非常感谢
Ah, thank you very much.
"麦克斯自制小蛋糕"
"Max's homemade cupcakes."
你知道谁会超级喜欢你们的小蛋糕吗
Well, you know who'd really like that cupcake?
瘾君子
Stoners.
她念了"麦克斯自制小蛋糕"这名字
She said "Max's homemade cupcakes."
玛莎·斯图尔特喜欢我们的小蛋糕
Martha Stewart likes our cupcakes!